

ryan.fadhilah.acc@gmail.com © 081929210000 🗘 https://github.com/ryanfadhilah

Graduate at December 2022 of Information System majoring in Business Information Technology at Bina Nusantara University. With around two years of working experience and Professional Certificate of Front-End developer at Meta. I have decided to fully commit on becoming a Full-Stack Developer that Specialized on Front-End.

# **EDUCATION**

## **BINA NUSANTARA UNIVERSITY**

Bachelor degree | 2018 - 2022

Computer Science majoring Business Information Technology - GPA 3.35

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### **FULL TIME - FINANCE ADMINISTRATOR**

Transindo Primatama | 3 months | Mar 2022 - Mar 2023

- Manage & Improve Financial System (Digitalization)
- Marketing & Client Service
- Cost Control

#### **INTERNSHIP - WEBSITE ASSISTANCE**

PricewaterhouseCoopers | 7 months | Mar 2021 - Sep 2021

- Newsletter distribution for Indonesia Infrastructure News.
- Provided technical support for Marketing and Communications Media on the website.
- Enhanced website and newsletter aesthetics through photo editing.
- Compiled insightful website analytics documentation.

## CERTIFICATES

## Meta Introduction to Front-End Development | Nov 2022

Professional Certificate | Credential ID G8JVPPA68JF9

- Verify at: https://coursera.org/verify/G8JVPPA68JF9
- Skills : Web Development Tools, User Interface, Front-End Web Development, HTML and CSS, Responsive Web Design.

## Meta HTML and CSS in Depth | Nov 2022

Professional Certificate | Credential ID XY778ZGECGG2

- Verify at: https://coursera.org/verify/XY778ZGECGG2
- Skills: Debugging, User Interface, React (Web Framework), HTML and CSS, JavaScript.

## Meta Programming With Javascript | Nov 2022

Professional Certificate | Credential ID FXTUAM4X9CR8

- Verify at: https://coursera.org/verify/FXTUAM4X9CR8
- Skills : Test-Driven Development, JavaScript, Front-End Web Development, Object-Oriented Programming (OOP).

## Meta Version Control | Nov 2023

Professional Certificate | Credential ID RXHCAMWJT45V

- Verify at : https://coursera.org/verify/RXHCAMWJT45V
- Skills: Linux, Web Development, Bash (Unix Shell), Github, Version Control.

# **SKILLS**

■ Website Analyst (Adobe Experience Manager, Data Visualization)	Intermediate
■ Front-End (React, Next.js, Typescript, Javascript, Redux, Tailwind, HTML, CSS, MySQL, Figma)	Intermediate
<ul><li>UML (Use Case Diagram, Activity Diagram, Sequence Diagram, Class Diagram)</li></ul>	Advanced
■ Microsoft (Word, Excel, Power Point, Virtual Agent, Visio)	Advanced
■ Graphic Design (Canva, Adobe Premier, Adobe Photoshop)	Advanced

# ORGANIZATION AND SOCIAL

#### **PROJECT MANAGER**

Teach for Indonesia Student Community | University Level | 7 months | Mar 2020 - Sep 2020

- Generate ideas for various event, such as campaign, seminar, and others
- Managing various events for Teach for Indonesia Student Community (TFISC)
- Instructor for Knowledge Management system and project planning for TFISC

#### **ACTIVIST OF CREATIVE DESIGN**

Teach for Indonesia Student Community | University Level | 1 Year 3 months | Jan 2020 - Mar 2021

- Create eye-catching designs such as posters, banners, certificates and uniforms.
- Volunteering weekly to teaching math and English to children at the Ballarenik Foundation.
- Serving as secretary and documentation lead for the Blood Donation BINUS @BEKASI in 2019.
- Effectively managing creative design benchmarking projects.

#### **PUBLIC RELATION OFFICER**

HIMSISFO | University Level | 2 Year 7 months | Sep 2018 - Mar 2021

- Being MC for various events.
- Teaching public speaking to junior member.